<resources>

    <string name="diurnalEffects">SleepBetter</string>
    <string name="nocturnalEffects">SleepBetter</string>


    <string name="app_name">SleepBetter</string>
    <string name="introductionTitle">WELCOME</string>
    <string name="welcomeTitle">Welcome to.... Here....</string>
    <string name="startButton">START</string>
    <string name="permission">Permission to run in the background</string>
    <string name="yourName">Your name...</string>
    <string name="linkBitmoji">Link your Bitmoji!</string>

    <string name="questionnaireTitle">QUESTIONNAIRE</string>
    <string name="questionnaireHelp">First, how would you rate the following aspects of your everyday life?</string>
    <string name="nocturnalTitle">Night-time</string>
    <string name="timesWakingUp">How many times do you wake up per night?</string>
    <string name="nightTerrorUsually">How often do you have night terrors?</string>
    <string name="beforeAfter">Before and after</string>
    <string name="fallAsleepUsually">How easily do you usually fall asleep?</string>
    <string name="wakeUpUsually">How easily do you usually wake up?</string>
    <string name="freshUsually">How fresh do you usually feel after you wake up?</string>
    <string name="mood">Mood</string>

    <string name="happyUsually">How happy do you usually feel during the day?</string>
    <string name="sadUsually">How sad do you usually feel during the day?</string>
    <string name="sleepyUsually">How sleepy do you usually feel during the day?</string>
    <string name="tiredUsually">How tired do you usually feel during the day?</string>
    <string name="stressUsually">How stressed do you usually feel during the day?</string>
    <string name="irritableUsually">How irritable do you usually feel during the day?</string>
    <string name="actions">Actions</string>
    <string name="concentrateUsually">How hard is for you to concentrate during the day?</string>
    <string name="coordinateUsually">How hard is for you to coordinate your activities during the day?</string>
    <string name="apetiteUsually">How would you usually rate your appetite during the day?</string>

    <string name="offquestionnaireHelp">How would you rate the following aspects of your day?</string>
    <string name="offtimesWakingUp">How many times did you wake up last night?</string>
    <string name="offnightTerrorUsually">How many night terrors did you have last night?</string>
    <string name="offfallAsleepUsually">How easily did you fall asleep last night?</string>
    <string name="offwakeUpUsually">How easily did you wake up this morning?</string>
    <string name="offfreshUsually">How fresh did you feel after you woke up today?</string>

    <string name="offhappyUsually">How happy did you feel today?</string>
    <string name="offsadUsually">How sad did you feel today?</string>
    <string name="offsleepyUsually">How sleepy did you feel today?</string>
    <string name="offtiredUsually">How tired did you feel today?</string>
    <string name="offstressUsually">How stressed did you feel today?</string>
    <string name="offirritableUsually">How irritable did you feel today?</string>
    <string name="offconcentrateUsually">How hard was for you to concentrate today?</string>
    <string name="offcoordinateUsually">How hard was for you to coordinate your activities today?</string>
    <string name="offapetiteUsually">How would you rate your appetite for today?</string>



    <string name="goalDiaryTitle">GOAL DIARY</string>
    <string name="greatText">GREAT! Here is your current avatar, reflecting your current state:</string>
    <string name="pleaseInputGoal">Please input either a goal, a wish, or any note. You can return to this section later.</string>
    <string name="goalInput">Goal Diary input...</string>


    <string name="main">MAIN</string>




    <string name="some_explanation_about_the_input">description</string>
    <string name="desc">Description</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main_page">MainPage</string>
    <string name="title_section1">Section 1</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Section 2</string>
    <string name="title_section3">Section 3</string>


    <string name="action_example">Example action</string>

    <string name="title_activity_main_menu">MainMenu</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="factorsTitle">FACTORS</string>
    <string name="factorsIntroduction">These are the next factors that impact your sleep hygiene. The checked ones are the ones you chose as targeted factors.</string>
    <string name="sleepSettings">SLEEP SETTINGS</string>
    <string name="lightCheck">Light</string>
    <string name="temperatureCheck">Temperature</string>
    <string name="noiseCheck">Noise</string>
    <string name="drugEffects">DRUG EFFECTS</string>
    <string name="nicotineCheck">Nicotine</string>
    <string name="alcoholCheck">Alcohol</string>
    <string name="homeostaticDrive">HOMEOSTATIC DRIVE</string>
    <string name="daytimeNapsCheck">Daytime naps</string>
    <string name="circadianRythms">CIRCADIAN RYTHMS</string>
    <string name="sleepingScheduleCheck">Sleep schedule</string>
    <string name="caffeineCheck">Caffeine</string>


    <string name="sleepSettingsTitle">Sleep Settings</string>
    <string name="lightIntro">Here you can mark which experiments you wish to undertake in terms of the LIGHT factor. You can also choose your own personalised behavior by clicking on PERSONALISED and having access to information.</string>
    <string name="lightTitle">LIGHT</string>
    <string name="firstLight">Increase bright light exposure during the day</string>
    <string name="secondLight">Wear glasses that block blue light during the night.</string>
    <string name="thirdLight">Turn off any bright lights 2 hours before going to bed (such as TV/the computer etc).</string>

    <string name="personalised">PERSONALISED</string>
    <string name="personalisedText">You currently have no personalised plan for this factor.</string>

    <string name="lightPersTitle">LIGHT - PERSONALISED PLAN</string>

    <string name="chatbotTitle">CHATBOT</string>



    <string name="drugEffectsTitle">Drug Effects</string>




    <string name="caffeineIntro">Here you can mark which experiments you wish to undertake in terms of the CAFFEINE factor. You can also choose your own personalised behavior by clicking on PERSONALISED and having access to information.</string>
    <string name="caffeineTitle">CAFFEINE</string>
    <string name="firstCaffeine">Do not drink caffeine within 6 hours before sleep</string>
    <string name="secondCaffeine">Limit yourself to 4 cups of coffees per day; 10 cans of coke/fanta; 2 energy drinks</string>
    <string name="thirdCaffeine">Do not drink caffeine on empty stomach</string>




    <string name="circadianRythmsTitle">Circadian Rythms</string>

    <string name="scheduleIntro">Here you can mark which experiments you wish to undertake in terms of the SLEEP SCHEDULE factor. You can also choose your own personalised behavior by clicking on PERSONALISED and having access to information.</string>
    <string name="scheduleTitle">SLEEP SCHEDULE</string>
    <string name="firstSchedule">Usually get up at the same time everyday, even on weekends/vacations</string>
    <string name="secondSchedule">Sleep no less than 7 hours per night</string>
    <string name="thirdSchedule">Do not go to bed unless you are tired. If you are not, relax with a bath/by reading a book before bed</string>
    <string name="fourthSchedule">Go to sleep at 22:30 PM the latest</string>

    <string name="schedulePersTitle">SLEEP SCHEDULE - PERSONALISED PLAN</string>
    <string name="persInputSchedule"> </string>


    <string name="goalDiaryIntro">Welcome to your Goal Diary! Here you will abe to note any particular changes you want to reflect on/any goals you wish to accomplice and any other observations. You can also see previous notes.</string>
    <string name="previousGoals">Previous notes</string>

    <string name="moreInfo">More Information</string>

    <string name="dataTitle">DATA</string>
    <string name="dataIntro">Here you will be able to look at personal data in terms of progress, changes, variations and so on! Below you will find 3 categories of data visualisation:\nProgress bar - where you will be able to see your current state on the way to your goal;\nTimelines - looking at your progress;\nSingle value displays - looking at your current state.  </string>
    <string name="progressTitle">Progress</string>
    <string name="timelineTitle">Timelines</string>
    <string name="singleValueDisplayTitle">Single Value Display</string>

       <string name="experimentTitle">EXPERIMENT</string>
    <string name="lightSubTitle">Light</string>
    <string name="caffeineSubTitle">Caffeine</string>
    <string name="scheduleSubTitle">Schedule</string>
    <string name="logging">LOGGING</string>
    <string name="dayReview">DAY REVIEW</string>
    <string name="question">Do you think you feel better than yesterday?</string>


    <string name="brightExposureIntro">Your current experiment is: INCREASE BRIGHT LIGHT EXPOSURE DURING THE DAY. Below you are asked to complete the questions on whether you followed the experiment.</string>
    <string name="morningQuestion">Did you get sunlight exposure in the morning?</string>
    <string name="outQuestion">Did you stay at least half an hour in the sun today?</string>
    <string name="sunlightQuestion">Did you keep your room so that it captures sunlight?</string>



    <string name="stopTVIntro">Your current experiment is: STOP WATCHING THE TV/THE COMPUTER WITHIN 2 HOURS OF GOING TO SLEEP. Below you are asked to complete the questions on whether you followed the experiment.</string>
    <string name="turnOffQuestion">Did you watch TV or stayed on the computer with 2 hours before going to bed?</string>

    <string name="turnOffIntro">Your current experiment is: TURN OFF ANY BRIGHT LIGHT WITHIN 2 HOURS OF GOING TO SLEEP. Below you are asked to complete the questions on whether you followed the experiment.</string>
    <string name="turnOffLightQuestion">Did you turn off any bright lights in your room with 2 hours before going to bed?</string>

    <string name="glassesIntro">Your current experiment is: WEAR GLASSES THAT BLOCK ANY LIGHT DURING THE NIGHT. Below you are asked to complete the questions on whether you followed the experiment.</string>
    <string name="dayQuestion">Did you use the f.lx app on the computer during  the day?</string>
    <string name="nightQuestion">Did you use any glasses to block blue light durign the night?</string>

    <string name="stomachIntro">Your current experiment is: DO NOT DRINK CAFFEINE ON EMPTY STOMACH. Below you are asked to complete the questions on whether you followed the experiment.</string>
    <string name="drinkCaffeineQuestion">Did you drink any caffeine today?</string>
    <string name="eatQuestion">If yes, did you do it on empty stomach?</string>

    <string name="limitIntro">Your current experiment is: Limit yourself to 4 cups of coffees per day; 10 cans of coke/fanta; 2 energy drinks. Below you are asked to complete the questions on whether you followed the experiment.</string>
    <string name="cupsQuestion">How many cups of coffee did you have today?</string>
    <string name="cansQuestion">How many cans of soda did you have today??</string>
    <string name="energydrinksQuestion">How many energy drinks did you have today??</string>

    <string name="sixIntro">Your current experiment is: DO NOT DRINK CAFFEINE WITHIN 6 HOURS OF GOING TO SLEEP. Below you are asked to complete the questions on whether you followed the experiment.</string>
    <string name="lastCoffeeQuestion">When did you have your last drink of caffeine? (soda/coffee/energy drink)</string>
    <string name="whenSleepQuestion">When did you go to sleep?</string>


    <string name="relaxIntro">Your current experiment is: Do not go to bed unless you are tired. If you are not, relax with a bath/by reading a book before bed. Below you are asked to complete the questions on whether you followed the experiment.</string>
    <string name="tiredQueston">Did you go to sleep fully relaxed/ready to sleep?</string>
    <string name="whatActivityQuestion">What activity of the next did you do before going to sleep?</string>
    <string name="bathAnswer">Took a bath</string>
    <string name="readAnswer">Read a book</string>
    <string name="stretchAnswer">Streched/Short exercise</string>
    <string name="teaAnswer">Drank hot drink</string>
    <string name="noneAnsswer">None of the above</string>

    <string name="sametimeIntro">Your current experiment is: Usually get up at the same time everyday, even on weekends/vacatins. Below you are asked to complete the questions on whether you followed the experiment.</string>
    <string name="whenWakeQuestion">When did you wake up?</string>

    <string name="sevenIntro">Your current experiment is: SLEEP NO LESS THAN 7 HOURS PER NIGHT. Below you are asked to complete the questions on whether you followed the experiment.</string>


    <string name="factorsMenu">Factors</string>
    <string name="data">Data</string>
    <string name="questionnaire">Questionnaire</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="diary">Goal Diary</string>


    <string name="noAnswer">No</string>
    <string name="yesAnswer">Yes</string>
    <string name="submitUpdate">SUBMIT</string>
    <string name="nextButton">NEXT</string>


</resources>
