<resources>

    <string name="diurnalEffects">SleepBetter</string>
    <string name="nocturnalEffects">SleepBetter</string>


    <string name="app_name">SleepBetter</string>
    <string name="introductionTitle">WELCOME</string>
    <string name="welcomeTitle">Welcome to.... Here....</string>
    <string name="startButton">START</string>
    <string name="permission">Consent Form</string>
    <string name="yourName">Your name...</string>
    <string name="participantName">Participant ID...</string>
    <string name="linkBitmoji">Linked Bitmoji</string>

    <string name="consentPageTitle">CONSENT FORM</string>
    <string name="consentIntro">In order to proceed with the experiment, we will kindly ask you to look over the next paragraphs to understand your involvement into this study. Please initial the box(es) if you agree with the statement(s):
</string>
    <string name="permissionOne">I have read and understood the information sheet (26/11/2018 /Version 2.0) and have had the opportunity to ask questions about the study.</string>
    <string name="permissionTwo">I agree to take part in this research project and agree for my data to be used for the purpose of this study.</string>
    <string name="permissionThree">I understand my participation is voluntary and I may withdraw at any time for any reason without my rights being affected.</string>
    <string name="permissionFour">I understand my responses will be anonymised in reports of the research.</string>
    <string name="permissionFive">I understand that I may be quoted directly in reports of the research but that my name will not be used.</string>
    <string name="permissionSix">I understand that the information collected about me may be anonymised and used in future ethically approved research studies.</string>
    <string name="permissionSeven">I understand that information collected about me during my participation in this study will be stored on a password protected computer and that this information will only be used for the purpose of ethically approved research studies.</string>
    <string name="permissionEight">Would you agree on being contacted after the study in regards to possible outcomes/ in order to provide insights from your experience of participating in this experiment?</string>

    <string name="noticeTitle">NOTICE</string>
    <string name="notice">The next set of questions you will receive aim to assess your sleeping experience before using the SleepBetter app, in order to be able to record your progress. There are 9 questions which should approximately take 1 or 2 minutes max.</string>


    <string name="op1">0-15 min</string>
    <string name="op1.1">I don\'t wake up too early/Up to 15 min</string>
    <string name="op2">16-30 min</string>
    <string name="op3">31-45 min</string>
    <string name="op4">46-60 min</string>
    <string name="op5">>60 min</string>

    <string name="op1.2">0-1</string>
    <string name="op2.2">2</string>
    <string name="op3.2">3</string>
    <string name="op4.2">4</string>
    <string name="op5.2">5/more</string>

    <string name="op1.3">Very good</string>
    <string name="op2.3">Good</string>
    <string name="op3.3">Average</string>
    <string name="op4.3">Poor</string>
    <string name="op5.3">Very poor</string>


    <string name="op1.4">Not at all</string>
    <string name="op2.4">A little</string>
    <string name="op3.4">Somewhat</string>
    <string name="op4.4">Much</string>
    <string name="op5.4">Very much</string>

    <string name="op1.5">I don\'t have a problem/less than 1 month</string>
    <string name="op2.5">1-2 months</string>
    <string name="op3.5">3-6 months</string>
    <string name="op4.5">7-12 months</string>
    <string name="op5.5">>1 year</string>


    <string name="op1.6">A lot worse</string>
    <string name="op2.6">Worse</string>
    <string name="op3.6">The same</string>
    <string name="op4.6">Better</string>
    <string name="op5.6">A lot better</string>

    <string name="questionnaireTitle">QUESTIONNAIRE</string>

    <string name="q1desc">This first set of questions refer to a general routine in your daily life. Please choose the most appropriate answer.</string>
    <string name="s1">How long does it usually take you to fall asleep?</string>
    <string name="s2">Usually if you wake up one or more times during the night, how long are you awake in total?</string>
    <string name="s3">If your final wake-up time occurs before you intend to wake up, how much earlier is this?</string>
    <string name="q2desc">This set of questions refer to your sleep quality in general. Please choose the most appropriate answer.</string>
    <string name="s4">How many nights a week do you have a problem with your sleep?</string>
    <string name="s5">How would you rate your sleep quality?</string>
    <string name="q3desc">This set of questions refer to the impact your sleeping pattern usually has on your daily activities and your life in general. Please choose the most appropriate answer.</string>
    <string name="s6">How do you think sleep negatively impacted your mood, energy, or relationships?</string>
    <string name="s7">How do you think sleep negatively impacted your concentration, productivity, or ability to stay awake?</string>
    <string name="s8">How do you think sleep negatively impacted your life in general?</string>
    <string name="q4desc">This set of questions aim to asses the severity of your sleep problems (if any). Please choose the most appropriate answer.</string>
    <string name="s9">How long have you had a problem with your sleep?</string>

    <string name="s1.1">How long did it take you to fall asleep last night?</string>
    <string name="s2.1">If you woke up one or more times during last night, how long are you awake in total?</string>
    <string name="s3.1">If your final wake-up time occurred before you intended to wake up, how much earlier was this?</string>
    <string name="s5.1">How would you rate the quality of last night\'s sleep?</string>
    <string name="s6.1">How do you think last night\'s sleep negatively impacted your mood, energy, or relationships?</string>
    <string name="s7.1">How do you think last night\'s sleep negatively impacted your concentration, productivity, or ability to stay awake?</string>
    <string name="s8.1">How do you think last night\'s sleep negatively impacted your life in general?</string>


    <string name="comments">Do you have any other notes you wish to add into your Goal Diary?</string>
    <string name="firstNote">*First note*</string>
    <string name="yourNote">Your note...</string>


    <string name="goalDiaryTitle">CURRENT STATE</string>
    <string name="goalDiaryTitlee">GOAL DIARY</string>
   <string name="pleaseInputGoal">Please input either a goal, a wish, or any note. You can return to this section later.</string>
    <string name="goalInput">Goal Diary input...</string>
    <string-array name="targetGraph">
            <item>Falling asleep</item>
            <item>Awake at night</item>
            <item>Waking up earlier</item>
            <item>Sleep quality</item>
        <item>Impacting feelings</item>
        <item>Impacting activities</item>
        <item>Impacting life</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="currentStatus">Current Status</string>
    <string name="goalStatus">Goal Status</string>
    <string name="youNeedToWorkOn">Fields that can be improved:</string>
    <string name="thingsToChange">Edit</string>

    <string name="svdyourOverall">Overall mood: edit</string>
    <string name="svdHowLong">How log it takes to fall asleep: edit</string>
    <string name="svdAwake">How long you are awake during the night: edit</string>
    <string name="svdEarlier">How much earlier you wake up than your normal time: edit</string>
    <string name="svdQuality">Sleep Quality: edit</string>
    <string name="svdImpactMood">Affecting mood, energy, or relationships: edit</string>
    <string name="svdImpactActivities">Affecting concentration, productivity, or ability to stay awake: edit</string>
    <string name="svdImpactGeneral">Affecting life in general: edit</string>
    <string name="svdExperiment">Experiment: edit</string>

    <string name="main">MAIN</string>


    <string name="some_explanation_about_the_input">description</string>
    <string name="desc">Description</string>
    <string name="goalDiaryInput">Goal Diary Input...</string>
    <string name="name">Your Name...</string>
    <string name="participant">Participant ID...</string>
    <string name="firstNoteHint">*First Note*</string>

    <string name="title_activity_main_page">MainPage</string>
    <string name="title_section1">Section 1</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Section 2</string>
    <string name="title_section3">Section 3</string>


    <string name="action_example">Example action</string>

    <string name="title_activity_main_menu">MainMenu</string>

    <string name="factorsTitle">EXPERIMENTS</string>
    <string name="settingsTitle">Settings</string>
    <string name="preQues">PRE-QUESTIONNAIRE</string>
    <string name="factorsIntroduction">
        These are the next factors and associated experiments that impact your sleep hygiene. The chosen experiment is the one you chose to follow.
        <font fgcolor="red"><b>Please bare in mind that after clicking Submit you will only be able to change the experiment after 5 days.</b></font>
        </string>

    <string name="sleepSettings">SLEEP SETTINGS</string>
    <string name="lightCheck">Light</string>
    <string name="temperatureCheck">Temperature</string>
    <string name="noiseCheck">Noise</string>
    <string name="drugEffects">DRUG EFFECTS</string>
    <string name="nicotineCheck">Nicotine</string>
    <string name="alcoholCheck">Alcohol</string>
    <string name="homeostaticDrive">HOMEOSTATIC DRIVE</string>
    <string name="daytimeNapsCheck">Daytime naps</string>
    <string name="circadianRythms">CIRCADIAN RYTHMS</string>
    <string name="sleepingScheduleCheck">Sleep schedule</string>
    <string name="caffeineCheck">Caffeine</string>


    <string name="sleepSettingsTitle">Sleep Settings</string>
  <string name="lightTitle">LIGHT</string>
    <string name="firstLight">Increase bright light exposure during the day</string>
    <string name="secondLight">Wear glasses/a sleeping mask that block blue light during the night.</string>
    <string name="thirdLight">Turn off any bright lights 2 hours before going to bed (such as TV/the computer etc).</string>

    <string name="caffeineTitle">CAFFEINE</string>
    <string name="firstCaffeine">Do not drink caffeine within 6 hours before sleep</string>
    <string name="secondCaffeine">Limit yourself to 4 cups of coffees per day; 10 cans of coke/fanta; 2 energy drinks</string>
    <string name="thirdCaffeine">Do not drink caffeine on empty stomach</string>


    <string name="circadianRythmsTitle">Circadian Rythms</string>

    <string name="scheduleIntro">Here you can mark which experiments you wish to undertake in terms of the SLEEP SCHEDULE factor. You can also choose your own personalised behavior by clicking on PERSONALISED and having access to information.</string>
    <string name="scheduleTitle">SLEEP SCHEDULE</string>
    <string name="firstSchedule">Usually get up at the same time everyday, even on weekends/vacations</string>
    <string name="secondSchedule">Sleep no less than 7 hours per night</string>
    <string name="thirdSchedule">Do not go to bed unless you are tired. If you are not, relax with a bath/by reading a book before bed</string>
    <string name="fourthSchedule">Go to sleep at 22:30 PM the latest</string>

    <string name="schedulePersTitle">SLEEP SCHEDULE - PERSONALISED PLAN</string>
    <string name="persInputSchedule"> </string>


    <string name="goalDiaryIntro">Welcome to your Goal Diary! Here you will able to note any particular changes you want to reflect on/any goals you wish to accomplice and any other observations. You can also see previous notes.</string>
    <string name="previousGoals">Today\'s notes</string>

    <string name="moreInfo">More Information</string>

    <string name="dataTitle">DATA</string>
    <string name="dataIntro">Here you will be able to look at personal data in terms of progress, changes, variations and so on!\nRatings - looking at your current state;\nImprovements - where you will be able to see what fields could be improved;\nTimelines - looking at your progress through 3 different types of graphs. </string>
    <string name="progressTitle">Improvements</string>
    <string name="timelineTitle">Timelines</string>
    <string name="singleValueDisplayTitle">Ratings</string>
    <string name="chooseTitle">Choose a timeline target!</string>
    <string name="info">INFO</string>


    <string name="experimentTitle">EXPERIMENT</string>
    <string name="lightSubTitle">Light</string>
    <string name="caffeineSubTitle">Caffeine</string>
    <string name="scheduleSubTitle">Schedule</string>
    <string name="logging">LOGGING</string>
    <string name="dayReview">DAY REVIEW</string>
    <string name="question">Do you think you feel better than yesterday?</string>


    <string name="brightExposureIntro">Your current experiment is: INCREASE BRIGHT LIGHT EXPOSURE DURING THE DAY. Below you are asked to complete the questions on whether you followed the experiment.</string>
    <string name="morningQuestion">Did you get sunlight exposure in the morning?</string>
    <string name="outQuestion">Did you stay at least half an hour in the sun today?</string>
    <string name="sunlightQuestion">Did your room capture the sunlight today?</string>


    <string name="stopTVIntro">Your current experiment is: STOP WATCHING THE TV/THE COMPUTER WITHIN 2 HOURS OF GOING TO SLEEP. Below you are asked to complete the questions on whether you followed the experiment.</string>
    <string name="turnOffQuestion">Did you watch TV or stayed on the computer with 2 hours before going to bed?</string>

    <string name="turnOffIntro">Your current experiment is: TURN OFF ANY BRIGHT LIGHT WITHIN 2 HOURS OF GOING TO SLEEP. Below you are asked to complete the questions on whether you followed the experiment.</string>
    <string name="turnOffLightQuestion">Did you turn off any bright lights in your room with 2 hours before going to bed?</string>

    <string name="glassesIntro">Your current experiment is: WEAR GLASSES/A SLEEPING MASK THAT BLOCK ANY LIGHT DURING THE NIGHT. Below you are asked to complete the questions on whether you followed the experiment.</string>
    <string name="dayQuestion">Did you use the f.lx app on the computer during  the day?</string>
    <string name="nightQuestion">Did you use any glasses/sleeping mask to block blue light during the night?</string>

    <string name="stomachIntro">Your current experiment is: DO NOT DRINK CAFFEINE ON EMPTY STOMACH. Below you are asked to complete the questions on whether you followed the experiment.</string>
    <string name="drinkCaffeineQuestion">Did you drink any caffeine today?</string>
    <string name="eatQuestion">If yes, did you do it on empty stomach?</string>

    <string name="limitIntro">Your current experiment is: LIMIT YOURSELF TO 4 CUPS OF COFFEE PER DAY; 10 CANS OF SODA; 2 ENERGY DRINKS. Below you are asked to complete the questions on whether you followed the experiment.</string>
    <string name="cupsQuestion">How many cups of coffee did you have today?</string>
    <string name="cansQuestion">How many cans of soda did you have today?</string>
    <string name="energydrinksQuestion">How many energy drinks did you have today?</string>

    <string name="coffee1">Less than 4 or 4</string>
    <string name="coffee2">More than 4</string>
    <string name="soda1">Less than 10 or 10</string>
    <string name="soda2">More than 10</string>
    <string name="energy1">Less than 2 or 2</string>
    <string name="energy2">More than 2</string>

    <string name="sixIntro">Your current experiment is: DO NOT DRINK CAFFEINE WITHIN 6 HOURS OF GOING TO SLEEP. Below you are asked to complete the questions on whether you followed the experiment.</string>
    <string name="lastCoffeeQuestion">When did you have your last drink of caffeine? (soda/coffee/energy drink)</string>
    <string name="whenSleepQuestion">When did you go to sleep?</string>


    <string name="relaxIntro">Your current experiment is: DO NOT GO TO BED UNLESS YOU ARE TIRED. IF YOU ARE NOT, RELAX WITH A BATH/READING A BOOK BEFORE BED. Below you are asked to complete the questions on whether you followed the experiment.</string>
    <string name="tiredQueston">Did you go to sleep fully relaxed/ready to sleep?</string>
    <string name="whatActivityQuestion">What activity of the next did you do before going to sleep?</string>
    <string name="bathAnswer">Took a bath</string>
    <string name="readAnswer">Read a book</string>
    <string name="stretchAnswer">Stretched/Short exercise</string>
    <string name="teaAnswer">Drank hot drink</string>
    <string name="noneAnsswer">None of the above</string>

    <string name="sametimeIntro">Your current experiment is: GET UP AT THE SAME TIME EVERYDAY, EVEN ON WEEKENDS/VACATIONS. Below you are asked to complete the questions on whether you followed the experiment.</string>
    <string name="whenWakeQuestion">When did you wake up?</string>

    <string name="sevenIntro">Your current experiment is: SLEEP NO LESS THAN 7 HOURS PER NIGHT. Below you are asked to complete the questions on whether you followed the experiment.</string>


    <string name="calendarTitle">CALENDAR</string>
    <string name="calendarIntro">The Calendar shows your progress in time. You will find that ecah day since the beginning of the experiment will be coloured in a representative way: the darker the red, the worse your state was/ the darker the green, the better your state was. By clicking on a specific date you will be able to se the overall mood, the experiment and the comments for that day.</string>

    <string name="factorsMenu">Factors</string>
    <string name="data">Data</string>
    <string name="questionnaire">Questionnaire</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="diary">Goal Diary</string>
    <string name="calendarMenu">Calendar</string>


    <string name="firstOptionMainMenu">WHAT IS SleepBetter?</string>
    <string name="secondOptionMainMenu">EXPERIMENTS AND FEATURES</string>
    <string name="thirdOptionMainMenu">CHATBOT GUIDE</string>

    <string name="mainMenuUp">Sleep Better works towards a tuning process over your sleeping patterns</string>
    <string name="introUp">FOR A BETTER YOU</string>
    <string name="introUpsub">Find your experiment</string>
    <string name="introDown">Sleep Beter @ Main Menu</string>

    <string name="whatISTitle">WHAT IS SLEEP BETTER?</string>
    <string name="WhatIsChatbot">You can ask Alex questions about sleep hygiene and other cool, interesting facts about sleep. For fun, you can also ask your companion to tell you a joke. just give it a try and have some fun!</string>


    <string name="sleepHygienetitle">Sleep Hygiene?</string>

    <string name="tuningTitle">Tuning - a process that works for you</string>
    <string name="tuning">What these sleep experiments are for, is to test the options that might work best for you to sleep better. You already sleep every day so you already have lots of practice sleeping - the goal in these experiments is to help you dial in ways that will help you sleep better.</string>
    <string name="sleepDescription">According to National Sleep Foundations, sleep hygiene is a variety of different practices and habits that are necessary to have good nighttime sleep quality and full daytime alertness. Obtaining healthy sleep is important for both physical and mental health. It can also improve productivity and overall quality of life. Everyone, from children to older adults, can benefit from developing a good sleep practice.</string>
    <string name="ourMissionn">Our mission with Sleep Better is to help you and guide you through a series of experiments that are proved to let you explore sleep hygiene. The Sleep Better app offers an easy-to-use, straightforward, friendly interface for you to use that would not only drive you through a self-experimentation tuning process but also help us identify the most impactful factors over your sleeping hygiene.</string>


    <string name="appIntro">Welcome! Sleep Better is a mobile application that guides you through a series of experiments that you can run in a definite period of time in order to start a tuning process over your sleeping patterns.
You will be able to change/choose your experiment once every 5 days, where (if you\'re in group A) at the end of each day you will have to log on your experience and analyse the data and interact with the other features of the app.
To begin with, complete the consent form, input your name (that only YOU will be able to see), and your given participant number.
</string>

    <string name="ourMissionTitle">Our mission?</string>
    <string name="howItWorksTitle">How it works?</string>


    <string name="howItWorks"> You can ask for more information on the following topics: Blue Screen, Caffeine, Circadian Rhythms, Energy drinks, etc! Simply ask your companion: \"Tell me about...\" and complete the question with one of the topics. You can also ask your companion for random facts about sleep: \"Tell me a fact\"! And do not forget to start with a Hi!</string>

    <string name="whatExeriments">WHAT EXPERIMENTS AND FEATURES?</string>
    <string name="experimentsTitle">Experiments</string>
    <string name="experiments">For the duration of the self-experimentation study, you will be able to choose which experiments you wish to conduct among the 10 options you have. At every 5 days, you will be required to either change the experiment or stick with it for another 5 days. You will be able to look at the data concerning your well-being in the DATA meu.</string>
    <string name="experimentsB">For the duration of the self-experimentation study, you will be able to choose which experiments you wish to conduct among the 10 options you have. At every 5 days, you will be required to either change the experiment or stick with it for another 5 days.</string>

    <string name="experiments2">The experiments will be split into 3 categories - LIGHT, CAFFEINE and SLEEP SCHEDULE. Each of them cover a different contextual factor  that has a direct impact on your sleep hygiene.\n  - Light looks at how either sunlight exposure and blue light impact your sleeping patterns;\n  - Caffeine looks at how drugs impact your system when it comes to bedtime;\n  - Sleep Schedule looks at how important a persistent schedule is towards a good seep.</string>
    <string name="loggingTitle">Logging</string>
    <string name="loggingExp">At the end of each day, you will be required to complete 2 short questionnaires (2-3 minutes in total) that would look at both how you approached the experiment in that day AND what is the outcome. The experiment logging asks you to rate whether you feel better/worse than yesterday, but also to answer a short series of questions on how you approached the chosen experiment (1-3 questions).</string>

    <string name="featuresTitle">Other Features</string>
    <string name="features">By easily navigating through the Sleep Better menu you can access each category that helps you explore your self-experimentation.\n \n FACTORS helps you choose you preffered experiment, at every 5 days.\n \n GOAL DIARY keeps track of every note you save regarding your experience. You are free to add whatever observation you might have at anytme. \n \n DATA gives you insights on how your well-being changed for the duration of the experiments - you can look at graphs, progress bars and current states. \n \n QUESTIONNAIRE will only be able to be accessed at the end of each day, when you will be asked to log in your status. \n \n CALENDAR will look on your progress throughout the experiment. You are also able to look at the status of that day by clicking on it.</string>

    <string name="chatbotGuide">CHATBOT GUIDE</string>


    <string name="chatbotintro">Start the conversation with a Hi, and then ask me about sleep hygiene topics (check the guide if you are not sure). If I do not reply, make sure you are connected to the internet.</string>



    <string name="noAnswer">No</string>
    <string name="yesAnswer">Yes</string>
    <string name="submitUpdate">SUBMIT</string>
    <string name="nextButton">NEXT</string>
    <string name="backButton">BACK</string>

    <string name="surveyDesc">All of this information is optional - and we’re making the gender question as open as possible - but it is important for the research questions that we can understand effects that may be related to gender in particular, and these other situational contexts. That said, while we would appreciate you helping us with as much of this information as possible, how much you complete is over to you. Please note none of your answers are ever connected with any identifiable information about you.</string>
    <string name="surveyTitle">SURVEY</string>
    <string name="genderd">Which gender do you identify most with?</string>
    <string name="gender1">Male</string>
    <string name="gender2">Female</string>
    <string name="gender3">I would prefer to not comment</string>

    <string name="aged">What is your age?</string>
    <string name="age1">18-24</string>
    <string name="age2">25-34</string>
    <string name="age3">35-44</string>
    <string name="age4">45-54</string>
    <string name="age5">Above 54</string>

    <string name="raced">What would best describe you?</string>
    <string name="race1">African American</string>
    <string name="race2">Asian</string>
    <string name="race3">Native American</string>
    <string name="race4">White</string>
    <string name="race5">Others</string>

    <string name="degreed">What is your highest qualification?</string>
    <string name="degree1">Less than high school diploma</string>
    <string name="degree2">High school diploma or equivalent degree</string>
    <string name="degree3">No degree</string>
    <string name="degree4">Bachelor’s degree</string>
    <string name="degree5">Master’s degree</string>

    <string name="maritald">What is your marital status?</string>
    <string name="marital1">Married</string>
    <string name="marital2">Divorced</string>
    <string name="marital3">Separated</string>
    <string name="marital4">Widowed</string>
    <string name="marital5">Unmarried</string>

    <string name="employmentd">What is your current employment status?</string>
    <string name="employment1">Full-time employment</string>
    <string name="employment2">Part-time employment</string>
    <string name="employment3">Unemployed</string>
    <string name="employment4">Self-employed</string>
    <string name="employment5">Home-maker</string>
    <string name="employment6">Student</string>
    <string name="employment7">Retired</string>

    <string name="incomed">Which income group does your household fall under?</string>
    <string name="income1">Less than $20,000</string>
    <string name="income2">$21,000 – $30,000</string>
    <string name="income3">$31,000 to $40,000</string>
    <string name="income4">$41,000 to $50,000</string>
    <string name="income5">$51,000 to $60,000</string>
    <string name="income6">Above $60,000</string>


</resources>
